# Teen Kar Seng

Email: teenkar@gmail.com Based in: Singapore

Phone: (+65) 9722 7928

## Professional Summary

I am a Junior year student at Berklee College of Music pursuing a Bachelor of Arts in Songwriting and Music Production.

I am highly proficient with ProTools and experienced in audio editing, mixing and sound design. I have worked on several student projects throughout my coursework. In particular, I found game audio to be one of my greatest strengths and developed passion for it. In addition, I can write and produce music for a variety of genres and use cases.

My other competencies include video editing, graphic design and photography, having graduated with a diploma in Communications & Media Management from Temasek Polytechnic.

## Portfolio Website

### https://tksaudio.com

#### Education

Bachelor of Arts, Songwriting and Producing Music, Berklee College of Music, Boston, Massachusetts.

April 2020 - Present

Current CGPA: 3.98

Diploma, Communications and Media Management, Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore.

April 2016 - May 2019 Graduated CGPA: 3.48

Skills

Sound Design **Avid ProTools Audiokinetic Wwise** Music Production **Music Writing FMOD Studios** HTML/CSS & JavaScript **Unity Engine (Basic)** 

Adobe Premiere Pro **Video Production** Adobe Photoshop Photography **Adobe After Effects** Microsoft Office

## Experience

### Freelance Audio Editor

May 2021

 Performed recording, editing and mixing of voice-overs for a college level prototype product design video.

#### Marketing Intern MediaCorp Pte Ltd, Singapore

April 2018 - September 2018

- Filmed and edited videos for social media marketing.
- Graphic Design to create posters and banners for use on digital website and printed for physical use.
- Collaborated with team members to help expand marketing channels.
- Monitored and analyzed impressions, reach and engagements on social media marketing campaigns.
- Handled social media accounts for company.

### Military

### National Service, Republic of Singapore Air Force (RSAF)

May 2019 - May 2021

• 2-year mandatory enlistment to the Singapore National Service with the RSAF.

### Language

- English (Spoken, Written) First Language
- Mandarin Chinese (Spoken, Written) Proficient

## Achievements

- MediaCorp Major Project Prize for Best Major Project Group, 2019
- 3rd Place at POL-ITE Water Polo competition, 2017 & 2018
- The Dream Composition Songwriting Competition Finalist, 2018
- 4th Place at National B Division Floorball competition, 2015